Zadanie B

B.1. Search for 'prowly' on Google with date filtering set to "Past year"

1. Open web browser.
Result: Web browser is open.
2. Go to https://www.google.com.
Result: Google homepage is loaded successfully.
3. In the search bar enter the keyword 'prowly' and press "Enter".
Result: Search results page is displayed.
4. Click on "Tools" to open the search tools menu.
Result: Available filters are displayed below "Tools".
5. Click on "Any time" to open the date filtering options.
Result: Dropdown with available options is displayed.
6. Set date range to "Past year".
Result: The search results are filtered according to the selected date range.


